Henry Y. Porter Theater Memorabilia Collection MS003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Artists and other celebrities; prints, photographs, and artifacts, 1722 -- 1990; 1880 -- 1920; MS003.001; 33.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Large cabinet cards, 11x14, opera singers, women, autographed, 1899 -- 1909; MS003.001.022.001 (Box 22)
    All autographed. All pictures had been previously framed.
    Ackte, Aino; Adams, Suzanne; Rondez, Maud; Bauermeister, Mathilde; Brema, Marie; Bridewell, Carrie; Calve, Emma; De Lussan, Zelie; de Pasquali, Bernice; Destinn, Emmy; Eames, Emma; Engle, Marie; Farrar, Geraldine; Fremstad, Olive; Gadski, Johanna; Garden, Mary; Lehmann, Lilli; MacIntyre, Margaret; Mantelli, Eugenia; Morena, Berta; Nordica, Lillian; Olitzka, Rosa; Rappold, Marie; Reuss-Belce, Luise; Sapio, Clemetine de Vere; Schumann-Heink, Ernestine; Sembrich, Marcella; Strong, Susan; Tornia, RIta; Walker, Edyth
  - Large cabinet cards, 11x14, opera singers, male, autographed, 1899 -- 1910; MS003.001.023.001 (Box 23)
    All autographed. All pictures had been previously framed. Inventory available.
    Albers, Henri; Alvaraez, Albert; Anthes, George; Bertram, Theodor; Bispham, David; Blass, Robert; Bonci, Alessandro; Burgstaller, Alois; Campanari, Guiseppe; Caruso, Enrico; Conried, Heinrich; Cremonini, Guiseppe; Dani, Carlos; De Marchi, Emilio; de Reszke, Edouard; de Reszke, Jean; Dippel, Andreas; Gilibert, Charles; Grau, Maurice; Journet, Marcel; Mahler, Gustav; Mancinelle, Luigi; Maurel, Victor; Muhlmann, Adolf; Plancon, Pol; Puccini, Giacomo; Saleza, Albert; Salignar, E. Thomas; Scotti, Antonio; Von Bandowski, Alexander; Van Dyck, Ernest; Van Rooy, Anton
  - Cartes de visite, actresses, women opera singers and some women musicians, 1870 -- 1899; MS003.001.024.001 (Box 24)
    Alphabetized.
  - Cartes de visite, actors and male opera singers, 1850 -- 1900; MS003.001.025.001 (Box 25)
  - Cartes de visite, composers, male and female musicians, painters and unknown, 1870 -- 1899; MS003.001.026.001 (Box 26)
    Alphabetized. A lot of these are images on cartes de visite of people from the seventeenth and eighteenth centuries.
  - Etchings and engravings, 1784 -- 1935; MS003.001.027
    Unsorted, includes eight files with portraits and some broadsides.
    - 17th, 18th, 19th century performers, 1784 -- 1870; MS003.001.027.00001 (Box 27)
    - Political and some musical, 18th and 19th century, 1844 -- 1899; MS003.001.027.00002 (Box 27)
    - 19th century opera singers, women. Etchings from photographs., 1900; MS003.001.027.00003 (Box 27)
    - 19th century actors and actresses in Shakespearean roles, 1900; MS003.001.027.00004 (Box 27)
    - 19th century opera singers and popular musicians. Drawn from photographs., 1900; MS003.001.027.00005 (Box 27)
    - "The Ray," Boston, advertising John McCullough in Macbeth., 1879; MS003.001.027.00006 (Box 27)
    - "The Ray," Boston, advertsising John McCullough in Richard III., 1876; MS003.001.027.00007 (Box 27)
    - 19th century prints, broadsides., 1860 -- 1935; MS003.001.027.00008 (Box 27)
      Unsorted, includes broadsides featuring E. L. Davenport, Charlotte Cushman, Lawrence Barrett and John McCullough.
  - Cabinet Cards, composers, musicians, musical personalities, various performers and writers, 1870 -- 1924; MS003.001.028.001 (Box 28)
    Inventory available. This date is approximate.
    Abbey, Henry; Abecco, Raffelle; Abroasis (?); Adamowski, Joseph; Adamowski, Timothee; Altschuler, Modest; Armbruster, Carl; Auseley, Sir Frederick; Bellini; Bach; Bemberg, David; Benedict, Sir Jules; Berlioz, Hector; Bruch, Max; Bull, Ole; von Bulow, Hans; Busoni, Ferroccio; Buzzi-Pecchia, Arturo; Chopin; Cilea, Francesco; Conried, Heinrich; Creminini; Crouch, Frederick N.; Dengremont, Maurice; Dresser, Paul; Edwards, Julian; Elman, Mischa; Flotow; Franko, Nathan; Gatti-Casazza, Giulio; Gauthier, Charles; Gerardy, Jean; Gericke, William; Godawsky, Leopold; Gounod, Charles; Grau, Robert; Gruppe, Paulo; Henschel, Georg; Herbert, Victor; Hofmann, Josef; Homer, Sidney; Joseffy, Rafael; de Koven, Reginold; Kreisler, Fritz; Liberati, Alessandro; Liszt, Franz; Mapleson, James H.; Marteau, Henri; Mascaqui, Pietro; Mollock, Lester; de Pachman V.; Paderewski, Ignace J.; Patti, Carlo; Petchinkoff, Alexander; Perosi, Don Lorenzo; Rabot, Wilhelm; Reger, Max; Remenyi, Eduard; Rosenthal, Moritz; Rugno, Raoul; Safonoff, Wassily; Schiller, George; Schoeffel, John B.; Scott, Clement; Seifert, Emil; Sivori, Ernesto; Strakosh, Max; Susini, M.; Tessendon, William; Toscanini, Arturo; Tschaikowsky, Peter L.; Thomas, Theodore; Verati; Verdi; Vogel, Dr. Hermann; Volpe, Arnold; Wagner, Richard; Weingartner, Felix; Wilhelmj, August; Carreno, Teresa; Cole, Belle; Essikof, Annette; Hirlrum, Sophia; Mehlig, Anna; Schumann, Clara; Toedt, Matilda; The American Humorists; Boston Philharmonic Club; Bradley & Rulofson's Celebrities; Die Intimen bei Beethoven; The Flonzaley Quartet; Holman English Opera Company; Passionspiel Oberammergau; "Rebecca's Triumph"; "Rigoletto Quartette"; Satirical cartoons; The Sistine Chapel & Monsignor Antonio Rella; Ward & Vokes; Vokes, Margaret Daly; Weber & Fields; The Weber Quartet of Boston; Wilson & Plunket; Billings, Josh; Greenwood, Grace; Longfellow, Henry W.; Meltzer, Charles Henry; Shakespeare, William; Ward, Elizabeth Phelps
  - Oversize cabinet cards and photographs, 1880 -- 1913; MS003.001.029.001 (Box 29)
    List can be found in the inventories of cabinet cards for actors and actresses, opera singers, musicians and various groups. Also included signed post card of dancer, Mikhail Baryshnikov. This date is approximate.
  - Autographed postcards of singers, composers and musicians, 1875 -- 1975; MS003.001.030
    Inventory available.
    - Emanuel List (1891-1967), Austrian bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00001 (Box 30)
      This date is approximate.
    - Pavel Ludikar (1892-1970), Czech bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00002 (Box 30)
    - Josef von Manowarda (1890-1942), Austrian bass, 1900 -- 1942; MS003.001.030.00003 (Box 30)
    - Jose Mardones (1969-1932), Spanish bass, 1925; MS003.001.030.00004 (Box 30)
    - Richard Mayr (1877-1935), Austrian bass, 1927; MS003.001.030.00005 (Box 30)
    - Leon Rains (1870-1954), American bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Ezio Pinza (1892-1957), Italian bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00007 (Box 30)
    - Leon Rothier (1874-1951), French bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - Leon Rothier (1874-1951), French bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00009 (Box 30)
    - Italo Tajo (1918- ), Italian bass as Dulcamara, 1950; MS003.001.030.00010 (Box 30)
    - Giorgio Tozzi (1923- ), American bass, 1950; MS003.001.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - Giorgio Tozzi (1923- ), American bass, 1950; MS003.001.030.00012 (Box 30)
    - Ludwig Weber (1899-1974), Austrian bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00013 (Box 30)
    - Ludwig Weber (1899-1974), Austrian bass, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00014 (Box 30)
    - Herbert Witherspoon (1873-1935), American bass as Landgrave, 1900 -- 1935; MS003.001.030.00015 (Box 30)
    - Eugen d'Albert (1864-1932), 1900 -- 1932; MS003.001.030.00016 (Box 30)
    - Granville Bantock (1868-1946), English composer, 1900 -- 1946; MS003.001.030.00017 (Box 30)
    - Mrs. H. H. A. Beach (1867-1944), American composer, 1900 -- 1944; MS003.001.030.00018 (Box 30)
    - Johannes Brahms (1833-1897), German composer, 1890; MS003.001.030.00019 (Box 30)
    - Carl Busch (1862-1943), 1900 -- 1943; MS003.001.030.00020 (Box 30)
    - Cecile Chaminade (1861-1944), French composer, 1928; MS003.001.030.00021 (Box 30)
    - Gustave Charpentier (1860-1956), 1928; MS003.001.030.00022 (Box 30)
    - Leo Delibes (1836-1891), French composer, 1880; MS003.001.030.00023 (Box 30)
    - Vincent D'Indy (1851-1931), French composer, 2 photographs, 1878 -- 1928; MS003.001.030.00024 (Box 30)
    - Engelbert Humperdinck (1854-1921), German composer, 1890; MS003.001.030.00025 (Box 30)
    - Engelbert Humperdinck (1854-1921), German composer, 1920; MS003.001.030.00026 (Box 30)
    - Edvard Grieg (1843-1907), Norwegian composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00028 (Box 30)
    - Emerich Kalman (1882-1953), Hungarian composer, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00029 (Box 30)
    - Franz Lehar (1870-1948), Austrian composer, 1900 -- 1948; MS003.001.030.00030 (Box 30)
    - Franz Lehar (1870-1948), Austrian composer, 1900 -- 1948; MS003.001.030.00031 (Box 30)
    - Thurlow Lieurance (1878-1963), American composer, 1954; MS003.001.030.00032 (Box 30)
    - Antonin Dvorak (1841-1904), Czech composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00033 (Box 30)
    - Edward Elgar (1857-1934), English composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00034 (Box 30)
    - Ruggiero Leoncavallo (1858-1919), Italian composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00035 (Box 30)
    - Edward MacDowell (1861-1908), American composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00036 (Box 30)
    - Mana Zucca (1890- ), American composer, 1956; MS003.001.030.00037 (Box 30)
    - Pietro Mascagni (1863-1945), Italian composer, 1900; MS003.001.030.00038 (Box 30)
    - Jules Massenet (1842-1912), French composer, 1880; MS003.001.030.00039 (Box 30)
    - Jaques Offenbach (1819-1880),German composer, 1875; MS003.001.030.00040 (Box 30)
    - Serge Prokofieff (1891-1953), Russian composer, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00041 (Box 30)
    - Giacomo Puccini (1858-1924), Italian composer, 1920; MS003.001.030.00042 (Box 30)
    - Joachim Raff (1822-1882), German composer, 1880; MS003.001.030.00043 (Box 30)
    - Camille Saint-Saens (1835-1921), French composer, 1886; MS003.001.030.00044 (Box 30)
    - Edward Strauss (1862-1916), Austrian composer, 1880; MS003.001.030.00045 (Box 30)
    - Richard Strauss (1864-1949), Austrian composer, 1910; MS003.001.030.00046 (Box 30)
    - Richard Strauss (1864-1949), Austrian composer, 1933; MS003.001.030.00047 (Box 30)
    - Jean Sibelius (1865-1957), Finnish composer, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00048 (Box 30)
    - Jean Sibelius (1865-1957), Finnish composer, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.030.00049 (Box 30)
    - Robert Stolz (1880-1975), Austrian composer, 1920 -- 1975; MS003.001.030.00050 (Box 30)
    - Robert Stolz (1880-1975), Austrian composer, 1920 -- 1975; MS003.001.030.00051 (Box 30)
    - Igor Stravinsky (1883-1971), Russian composer, 1910; MS003.001.030.00052 (Box 30)
    - Deems Taylor (1885-1966), American composer, 1950; MS003.001.030.00053 (Box 30)
    - Ernest Ansermet (1883-1969), Swiss conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00055 (Box 30)
    - Karl Bohm (1894-1981), Austrian conductor, 1966; MS003.001.030.00056 (Box 30)
    - Andre Cluytens (1905-1967), Belgian conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00057 (Box 30)
    - Frank Damrosch (1859-1937), American conductor, 1900; MS003.001.030.00058 (Box 30)
    - Sir Adrian Boult (1889-1983), English conductor, 1935; MS003.001.030.00059 (Box 30)
    - Eleazar de Cavalho (1915-1996), Brazilian conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00060 (Box 30)
    - Antol Dorati (1906-1988), Hungarian conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00061 (Box 30)
    - Aldo Franchetti (1883-1948), Italian conductor, 1910; MS003.001.030.00062 (Box 30)
    - Isidore Godfrey (1901-1977), English conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00063 (Box 30)
    - Vladimir Golschmann (1893-1972), French conductor, 1940; MS003.001.030.00064 (Box 30)
    - Sir Hamilton Harty (1879-1941), Irish conductor, 1927; MS003.001.030.00065 (Box 30)
    - Wilhelm Furtwangler (1886-1954), German conductor, 1940; MS003.001.030.00066 (Box 30)
    - Robert Heger (1886-1978), German conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00067 (Box 30)
    - Robert von Karajan (1908-1989), Austrian conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00068 (Box 30)
    - Joseph Keilberth (1908-1968), German conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00069 (Box 30)
    - Rudolph Kempe (1910-1976), German conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00070 (Box 30)
    - Josef Krips (1902-1974), Austrian composer, 1966; MS003.001.030.00071 (Box 30)
    - Rafael Kubelik (1914-1996), Czech conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00072 (Box 30)
    - Eugen Jochum (1902-1987), German conductor, 1974; MS003.001.030.00073 (Box 30)
    - Gustav Mahler (1860-1971), Bohemian conductor, 1890; MS003.001.030.00074 (Box 30)
    - Zubin Mehta (1936- ), Indian conductor, 1960; MS003.001.030.00075 (Box 30)
    - Bernardino Molinari (1880-1952), Italian conductor, 1930; MS003.001.030.00076 (Box 30)
    - Feliz Mottl (1856-1911), Austrian conductor, 1890; MS003.001.030.00077 (Box 30)
    - Willem Mengelberg (1871-1951), Dutch conductor, 1900; MS003.001.030.00078 (Box 30)
    - Dr. Karl Muck (1859-1940), German conductor, 1920; MS003.001.030.00079 (Box 30)
    - Arthur Nikisch (1855-1922), Hungarian conductor, 1890; MS003.001.030.00080 (Box 30)
    - Angelo Neumann (1838-1910), Austrian conductor, 1890; MS003.001.030.00081 (Box 30)
    - Emil Oberhoffer (1867-1933), German conductor, 1928; MS003.001.030.00082 (Box 30)
    - Paul Paray (1886-1979), French conductor, 1960; MS003.001.030.00083 (Box 30)
    - Bernhard Paumgartner (1897-1971), Austrian conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00084 (Box 30)
    - Emil Pollack (1979-1933), Czech conductor, 1930; MS003.001.030.00085 (Box 30)
    - Argeo Quadri, Italian conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00086 (Box 30)
    - Fritz Reiner (1888-1963), Hungarian conductor, 1910; MS003.001.030.00087 (Box 30)
    - Sir Landon Ronald (1873-1938), English conductor, 1924; MS003.001.030.00088 (Box 30)
    - Wassily Safonoff (1850-1918), Russian conductor, 1900; MS003.001.030.00089 (Box 30)
    - Sir Malcolm Sargent (1895-1967), English conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00090 (Box 30)
    - Wolfgang Sawallisch (1923- ), German conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00091 (Box 30)
    - Hans Schmidt-Isserstedt (1900-1973), German conductor, 1965; MS003.001.030.00092 (Box 30)
    - Carl Schuricht (1880-1967), German conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00093 (Box 30)
    - Carl Schuricht (1880-1967), German conductor, 1966; MS003.001.030.00094 (Box 30)
    - Sir Georg Solti (1912-1997), Hungarian conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00095 (Box 30)
    - Josef Stransky (1872-1936), Czech conductor, 1900; MS003.001.030.00096 (Box 30)
    - Edward Van Beinumn (1901-1959), Dutch conductor, 1940; MS003.001.030.00097 (Box 30)
    - Frank Van Der Stucken (1858-1929), American conductor, 1900; MS003.001.030.00098 (Box 30)
    - Willem Von Hoogstraten (1884-1965), Dutch conductor, 1910; MS003.001.030.00099 (Box 30)
    - Arturo Vigna (1863-1927), Italian conductor, 1909; MS003.001.030.00100 (Box 30)
    - Bruno Walter (1876-1962), German conductor, 1929; MS003.001.030.00101 (Box 30)
    - Bruno Walter (1876-1962), German conductor, 1950; MS003.001.030.00102 (Box 30)
    - Sir Henry J. Wood (1869-1944), English conductor, 1925; MS003.001.030.00103 (Box 30)
    - Sir Henry J. Wood (1869-1944), English conductor, 1925; MS003.001.030.00104 (Box 30)
    - Wilhelm Bachaus (1884-1969), German pianist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00105 (Box 30)
    - Harold Bauer (1873-1951), English pianist, 1910; MS003.001.030.00106 (Box 30)
    - Leonard Borwick (1868-1925), English pianist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00107 (Box 30)
    - Teresa Carreno (1853-1917), Venezuelan pianist, 1903; MS003.001.030.00108 (Box 30)
    - Cecile Chaminade (1861-1944), French pianist, 1890; MS003.001.030.00109 (Box 30)
    - Artur De Groef (1862-1940), Belgian pianist, 1920; MS003.001.030.00110 (Box 30)
    - Vladimir de Pachman (1848-1933), 1923; MS003.001.030.00111 (Box 30)
    - Leopold Godowsky (1870-1938), Polish pianist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00112 (Box 30)
    - Mark Hamburg, (1879-1960), Russian pianist, 1908; MS003.001.030.00113 (Box 30)
    - Alberto Jonas (1868-1943), Spnish pianist, 1909; MS003.001.030.00114 (Box 30)
    - Louis Kentner (1905-1986), English pianist, 1960; MS003.001.030.00115 (Box 30)
    - Shura Cherkassky (1911-1995), American pianist, 1926; MS003.001.030.00116 (Box 30)
    - Ethel Leginska (1890-1970), English pianist, 1920; MS003.001.030.00117 (Box 30)
    - Theodor Leschetitzky (1830-1915), Polish pianist, 1910; MS003.001.030.00118 (Box 30)
    - Elly Ney (1882-1968), German pianist, 1910; MS003.001.030.00119 (Box 30)
    - Ignace Jan Paderewski (1860-1941), Polish pianist, 1890; MS003.001.030.00120 (Box 30)
    - Max Pauer (1866-1945), German pianist, 1890; MS003.001.030.00121 (Box 30)
    - Raoul Pugno (1852-1914), French pianist, 1904; MS003.001.030.00122 (Box 30)
    - Emil von Sauer (1860-1942), German pianist, 1928; MS003.001.030.00123 (Box 30)
    - E. Robert Schmitz (1889-1949), French pianist, 1923; MS003.001.030.00124 (Box 30)
    - Xaver Scharwenka (1850-1924), German pianist and composer, 1890; MS003.001.030.00125 (Box 30)
    - Mischa Elman (1890-1967), Russian violinist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00126 (Box 30)
    - Carl Flesch (1873-1944), Hungarian violinist, 1925; MS003.001.030.00127 (Box 30)
    - Fritz Kreisler (1875-1962), Austrian violinist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00128 (Box 30)
    - Jan Kubelik (1880-1940), Bohemian violinist, 1895; MS003.001.030.00129 (Box 30)
    - Joseph Joachim (1831-1907), Hungarian violinist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00130 (Box 30)
    - Jan Kubelik (1880-1940), Bohemian violinist, 1902; MS003.001.030.00131 (Box 30)
    - Wilma Neruda (1939-1911), Bohemian violinst, 1880; MS003.001.030.00132 (Box 30)
    - Kathleen Parlow (1890-1963), Canadian violinist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00133 (Box 30)
    - Pablo de Sarasate (1844-1908), Spanish violinist, 1893; MS003.001.030.00134 (Box 30)
    - Eugen Ysaye (1859-1931), Belgian violinist, 1915; MS003.001.030.00135 (Box 30)
    - Efrem Zimbalist, (1889- ), Russian violinist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00136 (Box 30)
    - Eugen Ysaye (1859-1931), Belgian violinist, 1915; MS003.001.030.00137 (Box 30)
    - Jean Gerardy (1877-1929), Belgian cellist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00138 (Box 30)
    - Joseph Hollman (1852-1927), Dutch cellist, 1900; MS003.001.030.00139 (Box 30)
    - August Van Biene, cellist, 1909; MS003.001.030.00140 (Box 30)
    - Carlos Salzedo (1885-1961), French harpist, 1923; MS003.001.030.00141 (Box 30)
    - Joseph Bonnet (1884-1944), French organist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00142 (Box 30)
    - William C. Carl (1865-1936), American organist, 1928; MS003.001.030.00143 (Box 30)
    - Clarence Eddy (1851-1937), American organist, 1924; MS003.001.030.00144 (Box 30)
    - Del Staigers (1898-1950), American cornetist, 1931; MS003.001.030.00145 (Box 30)
  - Singers, 8x10, baritones and basses, all signed, 1890 -- 1961; MS003.001.031
    - Herbert Alsen (1906-1978), German bass, 1939; MS003.001.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni (1900-1969), Italian bass, 1943; MS003.001.031.00002 (Box 31)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni (1900-1969), Italian bass, 1943; MS003.001.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni (1900-1969), Italian bass, 1941; MS003.001.031.00004 (Box 31)
    - Chase Baremo (1892-1973), American bass, 1940; MS003.001.031.00005 (Box 31)
    - Norman Cordon (1904-1964), American bass, 1937; MS003.001.031.00006 (Box 31)
    - Feodor Chaliapin (1873-1938), Russian bass, 1925; MS003.001.031.00007 (Box 31)
    - Andres de Segurla (1875-1953), Spanish bass, 1930; MS003.001.031.00008 (Box 31)
    - Adamo Didur (1874-1946), Polish bass, 1914; MS003.001.031.00009 (Box 31)
    - Fernando Corena (1916-1984), Italian bass, 1940; MS003.001.031.00010 (Box 31)
    - Deszo Ernster (1900-1981), Hungarian bass, 1947; MS003.001.031.00011 (Box 31)
    - Wilhelm Wade Hinshaw (1967-1947), American bass, 1900; MS003.001.031.00012 (Box 31)
    - Sydney Granville (1880-1959), English bass, 1940; MS003.001.031.00013 (Box 31)
    - Marcel Tournett, bass, 1929; MS003.001.031.00014 (Box 31)
    - Ludwig Hoffman (1885-1964), German bass, 1932; MS003.001.031.00015 (Box 31)
    - Alexander Kipnis (1891-1978), Russian bass, 1939; MS003.001.031.00016 (Box 31)
    - Alexander Kipnis (1891-1978), Russian bass, 1937; MS003.001.031.00017 (Box 31)
    - Virgilio Lazzari (1890-1953), Italian bass, 1924; MS003.001.031.00018 (Box 31)
    - Virgilio Lazzari (1890-1953), Italian bass, 1937; MS003.001.031.00019 (Box 31)
    - Emanuel List (1891-1967), Austrian bass, 1935; MS003.001.031.00020 (Box 31)
    - Emanuel List (1891-1967), Austrian bass, 1943; MS003.001.031.00021 (Box 31)
    - Pompelio Malatesta (1884-1960), Italian bass, 1936; MS003.001.031.00022 (Box 31)
    - Gerhard Pechner (1903-1969), German bass, 1945-46, 1945 -- 1946; MS003.001.031.00023 (Box 31)
    - Ezio Piriza (1892-1957), Italian bass, 1933; MS003.001.031.00024 (Box 31)
    - Ezio Piriza (1892-1957), Italian bass, 1950; MS003.001.031.00025 (Box 31)
    - Nicola Mascona (1907-1945), Greek bass, 1938; MS003.001.031.00026 (Box 31)
    - Leon Rathier (1874-1951), French bass, 1936; MS003.001.031.00027 (Box 31)
    - Henri Scott (?), American bass, 1922; MS003.001.031.00028 (Box 31)
    - Charles T. Tittmann (1882-1964), American bass,1923, MS003.001.031.00029 (Box 31)
    - Vittorio Trevisan (1869-1958), Italian bass, 1924; MS003.001.031.00030 (Box 31)
    - Herbert Witherspoon (1873-1935), American bass, 1922; MS003.001.031.00031 (Box 31)
    - Herbert Witherspoon (1873-1935), American bass, 1900; MS003.001.031.00032 (Box 31)
    - Herbert Witherspoon (1873-1935), American bass, 1925; MS003.001.031.00033 (Box 31)
    - Pasquale Amato (1878-1942), Italian baritone, 1900; MS003.001.031.00034 (Box 31)
    - Georges Bakkanoff (1882-1938), Russian baritone, 1925; MS003.001.031.00035 (Box 31)
    - David Bishpham (1857-1921), American baritone, 1900; MS003.001.031.00036 (Box 31)
    - Richard Bonelli (189?-1980), American baritone, 1927; MS003.001.031.00037 (Box 31)
    - Richard Bonelli (189?-1980), American baritone, 1942; MS003.001.031.00038 (Box 31)
    - Harry C. Browne (1878-1954), American baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00039 (Box 31)
    - John Brownlee (1901-1969), Australian baritone, 1934; MS003.001.031.00040 (Box 31)
    - Thomas Chalmus (1884-1966), American baritone, 1924; MS003.001.031.00041 (Box 31)
    - Guiseppe Campanari (1859-1927), Italian baritone, 1910; MS003.001.031.00042 (Box 31)
    - Royal Dadmun (1890-1964), American baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00043 (Box 31)
    - Royal Dadmun (1890-1964), American baritone, 1923; MS003.001.031.00044 (Box 31)
    - Louis D'Angelo (1888-1958), Italian baritone, 1936; MS003.001.031.00045 (Box 31)
    - Emilio de Gogoya (1874-1949), Spanish, American baritone, 1923; MS003.001.031.00046 (Box 31)
    - Guiseppe de Luca (1876-1950), Italian baritone, 1935; MS003.001.031.00047 (Box 31)
    - Guiseppe Danise (1882-1963), Italian baritone, 1923; MS003.001.031.00048 (Box 31)
    - Donald Dickson (1910-1972), American baritone, ca.1940, MS003.001.031.00049 (Box 31)
    - Hector Dufranne (1875-1951), French baritone, 1912; MS003.001.031.00050 (Box 31)
    - Nelson Eddy (1901-1967), American baritone, 1930; MS003.001.031.00051 (Box 31)
    - Wiefred Engelman (1905-1978), American baritone, 1937; MS003.001.031.00052 (Box 31)
    - Cesare Formichi (1883-1949), Italian baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00053 (Box 31)
    - Cesare Formichi (1883-1949), Italian baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00054 (Box 31)
    - Arnold Gabor (1888-1950), Hungarian baritone, 1937; MS003.001.031.00055 (Box 31)
    - Alfredo Gandolfi (?), Italian baritone, 1936; MS003.001.031.00056 (Box 31)
    - Dinh Gilly (1877-1940), French baritone, 1900; MS003.001.031.00057 (Box 31)
    - Otto Gortitz (1873-1929), German baritone, 1925; MS003.001.031.00058 (Box 31)
    - Louis Graveure (1888-1965), Belgian (?) baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00059 (Box 31)
    - Edward Habish (1885-1960), German baritone, 1936; MS003.001.031.00060 (Box 31)
    - Mark Harrel (1909-1960), American baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00061 (Box 31)
    - Percy Hemus (?), American baritone, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.031.00062 (Box 31)
    - Julius Huehn (1904-1971), American baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00063 (Box 31)
    - Herbert Janssen (1895-1965), German baritone, 1946; MS003.001.031.00064 (Box 31)